We are reaching the point of no return where blatant disregard for international humanitarian law
scars our collective consciousness.
As of this morning,
283 health care workers in Gaza have been killed.
The last two months has been the deadliest conflict in United Nations history,
with 133 of their staff members killed.
There have been 212 attacks on Gaza health care facilities since October 7th.
This includes 24 different hospitals that have been bombed by Israel,
over 100 ambulances that have been put out of service.
Israel has arrested dozens of doctors, their whereabouts remain unknown.
The head of the main hospital, Shifa Hospital in Gaza City,
Mohammed Abu Salmiya, has been under Israeli arrest since November 22nd.
Many other senior doctors have continued to be held by the Israeli military for almost two weeks with no charges and no one knows their whereabouts.
Rantezi Pediatric Subspecialty Hospital, bombed.
Al Nasser Pediatric Hospital, bombed.
Gaza's Only Eye Hospital, bombed.
Gaza's Only Mental Health Hospital, bombed.
Wafa Rehabilitation Hospital, bombed.
The senior's facility immediately adjacent to Wafa Rehabilitation Hospital, bombed.
Al Jura Children's Hospital, targeted with prohibited white phosphorus, October 12th.
Indonesian Hospital, the only hospital currently operating in the north, still trying to treat patients while being bombed.
Shifa Hospital, bombed.
The two medical schools in Gaza, Islamic University of Gaza, bombed.
Al-Azhar University Medical School, bombed.
Médecins Sans Frontières Ambulance Convoy, bombed.
Red Cross Ambulance Convoys, bombed.
Of 35 hospitals in Gaza as of this morning, 26 are non-functional.
Nine remaining only partially functional.
But they are operating at more than double their capacity, with critical shortages of basic supplies and fuel.
These facilities are also providing shelter to thousands of internally displaced people.
Palestine Red Crescent Society yesterday announced that operations of their ambulances in northern Gaza has stopped.
Due to depletion of fuel, hospital closures, it is now impossible to evacuate wounded people in the north.
Instead, those patients are left to die.
As of this morning, over 17,000 Palestinian people have been killed, including over 7,000 children.
There are at least 46,000 people injured, thousands of whom are critically injured.
There is insufficient hospital space to treat even a fraction of these patients.
Massively overcrowded United Nations shelters have become havens to spread infectious diseases, including a hepatitis A outbreak,
multiple meningitis outbreaks, lice, skin infections, and multiple diarrheal illness outbreaks.
The United Nations Human Rights Office has declared on December 5th the pattern of attacks that target civilian infrastructure
raises serious concerns about Israel's compliance with international humanitarian law and raises the risk of atrocity crimes.
There have been immeasurable numbers of violations of special protection to civilians, children, and medical personnel.
And widespread violations of international humanitarian law.
incoming particular ransom hats
account.
I ramen lives.
head연au
full son,
coke,
Joe Russo
Flematic
understanding
how
help
take
Job
a
home
Video